inthe80s.com 2001-06-04

# Privacy Statement for InThe80s.Com

---|---  
This site is run by a guy from [Woostah, Mass](http://www.worcestermass.com/) |   
---|---  
| 

* * *

I'm not hip and I'm glad, because I hate hip. Hip doesn't last. I was never hip.  
Meatloaf

* * *  
  
## Overview

InThe80s.Com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

## Address Collection

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies are used by our site for tracking the last date of your visit in order to display only the most current messages you have not seen yet. 

## Outside Links

This site contains links to other sites. **InThe80s.Com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

## Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Form Submissions

This site makes use of forms on it's pages in order for users to comment on pages and suggest information we may have missed. The name and email addresses are only used in order to contact the person submitting the information in case there is a question about the subject matter. We **DO NOT** save email addresses or share them with our advertisers in any form. 

## Mailing List

This site does maintain a monthly newsletter for subscribers who have opted into it. To unsubscribe, send a message to [eighties-unsubscribe@makelist.com](mailto:eighties-unsubscribe@makelist.com)

As the mailing list is hosted by an outside firm, we can not vouch for the privacy of the email addresses. **However** their current [privacy statement](http://www.makelist.com/info/privacy.html) does state they won't sell the addresses of their subscribers. **DO NOT** send a message to the site owner to be removed as this will not remove you from the mailing list. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact ChuckyG InThe80s.Com [chuck@worcestermass.com](mailto:chuck@worcestermass.com)
